(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
止まらないで
Don't stop
差し入れを贈ってくださった皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
To everyone who sent gifts, thank you very much!
ここに宣言します
I declare here
ステップ、ステップワイズ
Step, stepwise
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Please wait a while until the performance starts.
きっと やめるときも 健やかなるときもずっと
Surely, in sickness and in health, always
愛を歌い続けることを どうぞ誓います
I swear to continue singing of love
MCもダンスももっと追求します
I'll pursue MCing and dancing even more
ずっと推してもらえるアイドルになってみせます
I'll show you I can be an idol you'll support forever
ようこそ...
Welcome...
不安な未来も 私が照らすんだ
Even an uncertain future, I will light it up
それでも 落ち込んじゃう日は
Even so, on days when I feel down
思い出しているよ みんなのその笑顔その声
I'm remembering everyone's smiles and voices
HAPPY LUCKY SEVEN革命 Sun-Mon
HAPPY LUCKY SEVEN Revolution Sun-Mon
この先ずっと一緒だよね
We'll be together forever from now on, right?
約束 ほらね
It's a promise, see?
笑う門にそれ来たる
Fortune comes to those who smile
HAPPY BIRTHDAY 毎日がほら Tue-Wed Lucky day
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, every day is, see, Tue-Wed Lucky day
生まれ変わっても 迷わずに
Even if I'm reborn, without hesitation
君だけのアイドルになるよ
I'll be your idol only
何度も見つけてね ステップ、ステップワイズ
Find me again and again, step, stepwise
HAPPY LUCKY SEVEN革命 Sun-Mon
HAPPY LUCKY SEVEN Revolution Sun-Mon
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Please wait a while until the performance starts.
2026.01.10
Tokyo International Forum
with DJ ANKIMO
Are You Ready?
Dreams in Motion
New Year's Party 2026
みんなー！
Everyone!
楽しさに釣られ
Drawn by the fun,
うっかり探したら
When I happened to search
知らないあれやこれ
All sorts of things I never knew,
巡り会った
I happened to encounter
大変な挑戦も
Even tough challenges,
のんびり休息も
And relaxing breaks,
支え合って思い
We support each other,
伝染した
Sharing our feelings
未開拓でも
Though unexplored,
前を向いて
Facing forward,
小さな星に重ねた
I layered it onto a tiny star
絶えず途切れない
Without ever stopping,
笑い声の中を
Through the laughter,
進んで行こう さあ
Let's keep moving forward
教えて ほら全部
Tell me, look, everything
何回時計の針
No matter how many times
ぐるぐる回っても
The clock's hands turn,
話を聞くよ
I'll listen to your story
まだまだ終わらない
It's far from over yet,
この夢がきっとずっと
This dream will surely, always,
永遠に褪せることのない
Give you a time that
時を君にくれる
Will never fade for eternity
訪れた先で
At the places I've visited,
歓喜増えていく
The joy keeps growing,
すれ違った風に
Even the pain in the
痛みさえ
Passing breeze
そして世界中を
And let's involve
巻き込んでいこう
The whole world,
一人また一人
As one person after another
加わった
Joins in
どっかだよって
Wondering where it is,
街を探し
Searching the town,
双眼鏡覗いても
Even looking through binoculars,
分からない
I can't tell
迷っているのも
Being lost is also
それが醍醐味だって
Part of the fun,
言って行こう ねぇ
Let's say that, okay?
たくさんの思い出を
Holding onto many memories
零さないよう抱きしめて
So that I don't spill them,
宝物大切に
I'll keep carrying them
運び続ける
As precious treasures
出会えた瞬間に
At the moment we met,
こんな場所だよって
I'll show you this place,
ずっと広げ見せつけて行こう
Spreading it out forever,
次は君の元へ
Next, to where you are
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
さあ教えてほら全部
Come on, tell me everything
何回時計の針
No matter how many times
ぐるぐる回っても
the clock hands spin around,
話を聞くよ
I'll listen to you.
あなたなら終わらない
With you, this dream
この夢がきっと
surely won't end.
ずっと永遠に
Forever and ever,
褪せることのない
it won't ever fade,
時を君にくれる
I'll give that time to you.
La la la...
みんなかけ声もやってね！
Everyone, join in the chants too!
夢に詰め込んだ
Packed into a dream
揺れる感情
are swaying emotions.
勇気がいるけど
It takes courage, but
君にだけあげる
I'll give them only to you.
ほらほら一緒にいこうな
Come on, let's go together.
秘密の街を明かしていこう
Let's uncover this secret town.
深呼吸して分かったこと
What I realized after a deep breath
壮大に笑っちゃうくらい
was so grand it's almost funny.
最高を目指そう
Let's aim for the best.
うまくいかないことだって
Even when things don't go well,
強がりだって
even when I'm just acting tough,
明日の教科書見ずに閉じたら
if I close tomorrow's textbook without looking,
なんてやれそうだ
I feel like I can do it.
落書きの中に光ってた想いを
The feelings that were shining in the doodles,
君とこうして話せたなんて遊びたいから
I'm glad I could talk with you like this, because I want to play
もっと！
more!
また抱いてステップして
Hold me again and take a step.
未知の展開も悪くはないよね
Unknown developments aren't so bad either.
酸いも甘いも集めたの
I gathered both the sour and the sweet.
しようかな？
Should I?
準備できるかな？
Are you ready?
共に街を繋げあおう
Let's connect the town together.
弾む心 増える希望の中
Within a bouncing heart and growing hope,
いつまでも！
forever!
大好きは
Our love,
単純なままいこう
let's keep it simple.
楽しい過程にほら
In the fun process, look,
一瞬で向こう
we'll be over there in an instant.
昨日よりも加速してる
Accelerating more than yesterday.
ちょっと繋いでて
Keep us connected for a bit.
簡単じゃない本物の掛け声は
True chants aren't easy.
いつも君が高鳴る僕らだって支えてくれる
You always support us even when our hearts race.
ずっと！刻まれていくから
Forever! Because it will be engraved!
みんな一緒にせーの！
Everyone together, ready, go!
La la la...
うまくいかないことだって
Even when things don't go well,
強がりだって
even when I'm just acting tough,
明日の教科書見ずに閉じたら
if I close tomorrow's textbook without looking,
なんてやれそうだ
I feel like I can do it.
落書きの中に光ってた想いを
The feelings that were shining in the doodles,
君とこうして話せたなんて遊びたいから
I'm glad I could talk with you like this, because I want to play
もっと！
more!
また抱いてステップして
Hold me again and take a step.
みんな笑顔せーの！レッツゴーソラ！
Everyone smile, ready, go! Let's go Sora!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
おはよう！あてに今日もおご挨拶
Good morning! Another greeting addressed to you today.
てあれ？嘘！もうこんな時間？
Wait, what? No way! Is it this time already?
午後から予定あるのに
I have plans for the afternoon...
すぐに支度をしなきゃ！行ってきます！
...so I have to get ready right away! I'm off!
慌てて飛び出して気づく
I rushed out only to realize...
こっちじゃないここどこ？助けてあん肝！
...it's not this way! Where am I? Help me, Ankimo!
トラブルばっか転んで起きての毎日です
It's just trouble after trouble, falling and getting up every day.
何でも思い通りとかそんな美味しい話はないから
Things going exactly as planned—there's no such sweet deal.
心の曇り空を晴らす合言葉唱えて
Reciting the magic words to clear the cloudy skies of the heart...
ほら快晴でしょう！ずっと
See, it's perfectly clear! Always...
みんなに届けたい
...I want to reach everyone...
歌もダンスも元気も！
...with my songs, my dance, and my energy!
きっとおなじ空の下
Surely, under the same sky...
笑顔も分け合えるよ
...we can share our smiles.
ちょっと疲れちゃうときも
Even when I'm a bit tired...
涙が出そうなときも
...or when I'm about to cry...
いつも魔法の言葉で
...always with the magic words...
今日もケセラセラのかな
...today is 'Que Sera Sera,' I guess.
せーの！ケセラセラ！
One, two! Que Sera Sera!
みんなコンそら！
Hello everyone, KonSora!
今日も一日頑張ろう！
Let's do our best again today!
カメラにマイクによし準備オッケー！
Camera, mic—all set! Ready, okay!
お水もちゃんとあるし
I've got my water, too.
備えさえあれば嬉しいです
If I'm prepared, I'm happy.
それじゃ今日は何をしようかな？
Well then, what should I do today?
お歌に雑談に
Singing, chatting...
あ、ほらトラブルだ！
Oh, see, here's some trouble!
みんなと笑い飛ばせば
If I laugh it off with everyone...
また明日も晴れ晴れだ！よっしゃ！
...tomorrow will be bright again! Alright!
ほっと溜息こぼして
Letting out a soft sigh...
ふと夜空を見上げたら
...and happening to look up at the night sky...
ぽっと満天の星たちが
...suddenly, the stars filling the heavens...
キラキラ瞬いていた
...were sparkling and twinkling.
ずっと追いかけ続けたい
I want to keep chasing them...
雲より高い夢でも
...even if it's a dream higher than the clouds.
もっと強く羽ばたいて
I'll flap my wings even harder...
空まで駆けていくよ
...and run all the way to the sky.
そっと背中を押すような
When I'm wrapped in a warmth...
ぬくもりに包まれたら
...that feels like a gentle push on my back...
いつまでも止まんないよ
...I'll never stop.
今日も今日も、明日も明日も
Today and today, tomorrow and tomorrow...
ずっとケセラセラのかな
...it'll always be 'Que Sera Sera,' I guess.
せーの！ケセラセラ！
One, two! Que Sera Sera!
みんなー！
Everyone!
新年明けまして
Happy New Year...
おめでとうございまーす！
...everyone!
本日はお寒い中
Thank you for coming today...
ありがとうございます。
...despite the cold weather.
みんな来れた？あ、来れてるからいるのわかる。
Did everyone make it? Ah, I can see you're here, so of course you did.
ちゃんと安全に来れましたかー？
Did you all arrive here safely?
え、今回のそらパは、えっと、私のライブ史上最大規模ということで
So, this Sora Party is, well, my biggest live event ever...
すごい大きな会場で、あの、ハッシュタグとかも見てたんだけど
It's such a huge venue. I was looking at the hashtags, and...
「デカ！」って。
...people were saying, "It's huge!"
「デカいのすごいな」って書いてる人がいっぱいいて
Lots of people wrote, "It's amazing how big it is,"
私も「デカいな、すごいな」って思いながら見てました。
and I was also thinking "It's big, it's amazing" while looking at it.
リハーサルの時は「ここにいっぱいそらともさん来るね」って言われて
During rehearsals, I was told "Lots of Soratomos will come here,"
「え、誰もいないじゃん！誰もいないよ！
and I was like, "Wait, there's no one! No one's here!
誰もいない…」っていう会話をしながらとっても楽しくやっておりました。
No one..." We were having that kind of conversation and having a lot of fun.
でもみんないるね！ありがとう！
But you're all here! Thank you!
というわけで、今日初めてライブだよって人ー！
So, who's here for their very first live event?
おおー、結構いるね！
Ooh, quite a few of you!
じゃあ、現地自体初めてだよって人ー！
Then, how about those for whom being on-site is a first?
結構いる！ありがとう！
Quite a few! Thank you!
じゃあ頑張って、あ、手振るだけでいいからね。
Then please try—oh, just waving is fine.
女の子ー！
Girls!
声出してくれてありがとう！
Thank you for speaking up!
きゃー！聞こえた！
Kyaa! I heard you!
海外ニキニキー！
Overseas brothers!
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
え、これってあれ？ペンライトとかできるのかな？
Er, can we do the thing with the penlights?
まだできないのかな？できるかな？
Maybe not yet? Can we?
こちらの人、赤！
People on this side, red!
こちらの人は、青！
People on this side, blue!
真ん中は黄色！
The middle is yellow!
うわぁ、すごーい！
Wow, amazing!
綺麗だー！
It's beautiful!
こんな感じでですね、今日はペンライトでも
Just like this, we can even play with
遊べちゃうということで、ぜひぜひみんなでも楽しんでいきましょう！
penlights today, so let's all have fun together!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
今日はみんなも主役だよー！
Everyone is the main character today!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
まだ飲んでない！
I haven't drunk it yet!
お水可愛い、ありがとう。
The water is cute, thank you.
もうちょっと飲も。
I'll drink a bit more.
お水だってわかったじゃん、後ろ向いたから。
You knew it was water because I turned around.
えへへ、ありがとう。
Ehehe, thank you.
さ、というわけでね、今日はいかがだったでしょうか...
Now then, "how was today"...
とはいかないので！
is not how it's going!
始まったばかり！
It just started!
なのですが、なんと...言ってもいいのかな？
However, surprisingly... can I say it?
YouTubeの配信は...
The YouTube stream is...
なんと、ここまでなんです！
surprisingly, ends here!
始まったばかり！
It just started!
でも続き見たい人は、ここら...ここらへんに、
But for those who want to see more,
チケットが買えると思う...
I think you can buy tickets around here...
「買える」って言い方やだ、
I don't like saying "buy",
見に来てねー！
please come watch!
チカチカしておる、すごい。
It's flickering, amazing.
というわけで、先にどんどん行ってみましょうか！
So, let's keep going forward!
盛り上がってますかー！？
Are you hyped!?
楽しんでいってよ！
Have fun!
それでは盛り上がっていこうよ！
Alright, let's get hyped!
オキシドキシ エブリバディだけど
Okidoki, everybody, but
冒頭無料配信はこちらで終了です。
The free preview broadcast ends here.